atlanta-airport.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Statement

**IMPORTANT! PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE.**

**Revised: March 17, 2008**

Thank you for visiting atlanta-airport.com. The Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International Airport (“HJAIA”) strives to provide online resources in a safe, secure manner that respects your privacy when you visit our sites.

This privacy statement addresses the collection, use, disclosure, and security of information that may be obtained by the City of Atlanta. In using the HJAIA website, you agree to do so in accordance with the privacy policies of this statement. 

**Information Collected**

We collect no personal information about you when you visit the HJAIA Website unless you choose to provide this information to us. However, some information is collected and stored automatically. 

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the Website, read pages, or download information, the following information is collected and stored automatically from your visit:

  * The name of your domain; for example, "xyzcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account; 
  * An IP address; a number automatically assigned to your computer when you are using the Internet; 
  * The type of browser and operating system used to access our site; 
  * The Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site; 
  * The pages you visit within the portal; and 
  * The links made to other websites through the portal. 

This information is collected for statistical analysis using third-party or proprietary software programs to create summary statistics. The statistics are used for the purpose of determining what information is of most and least interest to all visitors and identifying system performance or problem areas in order to better plan future portal enhancements. This information is not collected for commercial marketing purposes.

If, during your visit to atlanta-airport.com, you voluntarily provide personally identifiable information, we will collect such information. Examples of personally identifiable information may include: 

  * Your name, address, or phone number; 
  * An email address if you are communicating to us through email; 
  * Information you voluntarily submit to the City of Atlanta for the purposes of completing or submitting an application or form online; 
  * Other information volunteered, such as vendor profile/contact information, survey information or content of email 

In general, please note the information collected, whether or not personally identifiable, is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video and other graphic formats you send us. Information is retained and used in accordance with existing laws, rules, regulations, and other policies.  
**  
Use**

Depending on the specific service or transaction, the City of Atlanta may share personally identifiable information amongst its agencies in order to provide such service or complete such transaction. **Personalization** You may choose or opt to voluntarily provide certain personally identifiable information in order to customize your visits to atlanta-airport.com. To personalize your experience, you may be required to register and create an online profile. Information required during the registration process will include a user name (which need not be your legal name), a password and a valid email address. The combined information will most likely constitute personally identifiable information. You may review, delete or modify such profile at any time. If you simply wish to view pages on atlanta-airport.com, or conduct most transactions, you are not required to use the personalization features. **Public Disclosure** We will not disclose any personally identifiable information collected to entities outside of City of Atlanta departments and agencies except where you have given us permission, or where the information is public information under the Georgia Open Records Act O.C.G.A. 50-18-70 et seq., or other applicable laws. Visitors should be aware that information collected through the portal may be subject to examination and inspection, if such information is a public record, or not otherwise protected from disclosure. **Cookies** The atlanta-airport.com portal may occasionally use "cookies" to customize your browsing experience. Cookies are simple text files stored by your web browser and they provide a method of distinguishing among visitors to the websites, and allowing customized features such as a "shopping cart" feature for online purchasing. Cookies created on your computer by using our websites do not contain personally identifiable information and do not compromise your privacy or security. You can refuse the cookie or delete the cookie file from your computer at any time by using any one of a number of widely available methods. **Security** Several tools, policies and protocols are used to safeguard the submission of information through the portal. Security measures have been integrated into the design, implementation and day-to-day operations of the entire operating environment as part of our continuing commitment to the security of electronic content as well as the electronic transmission of information.

For services requiring online financial transactions, atlanta-airport.com uses the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption protocol to safeguard your sensitive personal information, including your credit card number. Information is encrypted from your computer to the portal computer processing your request.  
In order to further secure your privacy, do not divulge any passwords or sensitive information (e.g. credit card number) to anyone in a phone call or email. When you are finished with those applications that are password protected or required the input of your credit card information, it is always recommended that you close or otherwise exit the browser page.

**Links to Other Sites**

Please note that agency sub-portals and/or specific pages may contain additional or different privacy statements. The HJAIA Website may include links to partner sites, especially other federal agencies. In a few cases we may link to private organizations. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new site. The City of Atlanta and HJAIA do not endorse, support or otherwise promote any private or commercial entity that may be reached through links on our Website.

The City of Atlanta and HJAIA make no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this Website and expressly disclaim liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this Website. No warranty of any kind, implied, expressed or statutory, including but not limited to opinions or statements made by third parties, information provided by individuals other than the Website operator, is given with respect to the contents of this Website or its hyperlinks to other Internet resources. 

**E-mail** E-mail is not a secure form of transmission. As such, atlanta-airport.com does not recommend that you submit sensitive or personally identifiable information via e-mail. If you choose to provide us with personal information in an e-mail we may use the email and the information contained within it to improve our service to you or to respond to your request. Sometimes, we forward your email to other City employees who may be better able to help you, and this staff may be employed by a different agency within the City. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations or as required by law, we do not share our e-mail with any other organizations outside of the public sector.

**Changes to This Privacy Statement**

Revisions to this Privacy Statement will be posted to this location so that you will know the type of information we collect and how that information is used. We will also post the last date of revision at the top of this page.

Our goal is to provide a private, efficient and friendly digital government experience. If you have comments or questions regarding privacy at atlanta-airport.com, please contact us at webmaster@atlanta-airport.com.
